picadmedia.com 2010-10-30

# Image Space Media - Privacy Policy

Image Space Media, Inc. ("Image Space Media") respects the privacy concerns of the users of its Website, www.imagespacemedia.com (the "Website"). Image Space Media thus provides this privacy statement to explain what information is gathered during a visit to the Website and how such information may be used. 

**Use of Information:** As a general policy no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, or e-mail address, is automatically collected from your visit to the Website. However, certain non-personal information is recorded by the standard operation of Image Space Media's Internet servers. Information such as the type of browser being used, its operating system, and your IP address is gathered in order to enhance your online experience. 

The Website may request that you give us contact information such as your name, mailing and/or e-mail address; demographic information such as your age and gender; and personal preference information. Information submitted at the time of submission will be used by Image Space Media only as necessary for our legitimate business interests, including without limitation the improvement of our products, services and the contents of the Website. Image Space Media may also share such information with our business and promotional partners to further those interests. Personally identifiable information is never sold or leased to any third parties. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information:** If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update it by emailing our Customer Support at [info@imagespacemedia.com](mailto:info@imagespacemedia.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

### Specific uses of information on the Website may include:

**Image Space Media's Inquiry Form**

The Image Space Media Website contains an "inquiry form" for web publishers to request additional information about Image Space Media's products/services. The inquiry form requires web publishers to give contact information (such as name and email address.) Image Space Media uses this information to contact Web Publishers about the services on the Website in which they have expressed interest. 

Web Publishers have the option to provide demographic information (such as website address and vertical sector) to Image Space Media. Image Space Media encourages them to submit this information so it can provide them a more customized reply to their inquiry. 

**Insertion Orders**

If an advertiser purchases a service from Image Space Media, Image Space Media requests certain personal and company identity information from the advertiser on the insertion form. Advertisers must provide contact information (such as name, company name, street address, email and telephone number) and financial information. Image Space Media uses this information to provide services and for billing purposes. If Image Space Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the advertiser. 

**Web Publisher Service Agreement**

If a Web Publisher signs a service agreement, Image Space Media requires the Web Publisher to provide certain identifiable information including: name, company name, street address, email and telephone number. This information is necessary to process the Web Publisher's agreement. 

**Web Publisher Sign-up form**

When a Web Publisher signs a service agreement with Image Space Media, the Web Publisher is also required to provide company and personal identity information, commercial information, technical contact information and customization information to start their in-picture advertising services. Image Space Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If Image Space Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Web Publisher. 

**Advertising Network Service Agreement**

When a Advertising Network signs a service agreement with Image Space Media, the Advertising Network is also required to provide company, personal identity information and commercial information. Image Space Media uses this information to provide services and for payment purposes. If Image Space Media has trouble processing an order, it will use this information to contact the Advertising Network. 

**Service-related Announcements**

Image Space Media will send Web Publishers service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. The only other e-mails we send out are in response to feedback, contact and sign-up form submissions. 

Generally, a Web Publisher may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If a Web Publisher does not wish to receive these communications, they have the option to deactivate their account according to the terms of their Web Services Agreement. 

**Customer Service**

Based upon the provided personally identifiable information, Image Space Media will send Web Publishers a welcoming email to verify their username and password and to set up their account. Image Space Media will also communicate with them in response to their inquiries, to provide the services they request, and to manage their account. Image Space Media will communicate with Web Publishers by email or telephone, in accordance with their wishes. 

**Testimonials**

If your name appears in a testimonial on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information displayed there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this website, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these testimonials. 

**Legal Disclaimer:**

Image Space Media may disclose user information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference (either intentionally or unintentionally) with Image Space Media's rights or property, other users of the Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. Image Space Media may also disclose user information when necessary to comply with a court order, legal process or other legal proceeding. 

**Children Age 12 and Under:**

Image Space Media recognizes the special obligation to protect personally identifiable information obtained from children age 12 and under. AS SUCH, IF YOU ARE 12 YEARS OLD OR YOUNGER, IMAGE SPACE MEDIA REQUESTS THAT YOU NOT SUBMIT ANY PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THE WEBSITE OR TO IMAGE SPACE MEDIA. If Image Space Media discovers that a child age 12 or younger has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete that child's personally identifiable information from our records. 

**Use of Cookies:**

Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual's computer hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies make using our Website easier by, among other things, saving your passwords and preferences for you. These cookies are restricted for use only on our Website, and do not transfer any personal information to any other party. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. Please consult the technical information relevant to your browser for instructions. If you choose to disable your cookies setting or refuse to accept a cookie, some parts of the Website may not function properly or may be considerably slower. 

**Links to External Websites:**

Image Space Media is not responsible for the content or practices of third party websites not owned or controlled by Image Space Media. Image Space Media is also not responsible for any information that you might share with such linked websites. You should refer to each such website's respective privacy policy and practices prior to disclosing any such information. 

**Choice/Opt-Out:**

The Website may provide you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us at the point where we request information about you. You always have the option of removing your name from any e-mail list in order to discontinue any such future communications. In order to ensure immediate removal from any list, please follow the specific instructions set forth within the communications you receive from Image Space Media which you no longer wish to receive. If you are unsuccessful in completing the instructions specified in any such communication, please e-mail us at [info@imagespacemedia.com](mailto:info@imagespacemedia.com) , including a copy of the undesired email attached to the request, and state you wish to be removed from the mailing list. 

**Contact Information for Questions, Comments and Complaints:** If you have any questions, comments or complaints about www.imagespacemedia.com or about this privacy statement, please contact us at [info@imagespacemedia.com](mailto:info@imagespacemedia.com).
